I'm staring at the terminal, the text is running
green. I bypass all the bloated menus,
cluttering the screen. The heavy server
humming in the closet down the hall. I'm
throwing diagnostics like a hammer at the wall.
I don't need a graphical design to set it right. I
am managing the gateway in the middle of the
night. I see the Vanguard waking up. I read the
data trace. The Crimson Node is sending out a
signal through the space. I'm locking down the
routing. I'm changing all the rules. I'm taking
all the bandwidth from the other level fools.
Quality of service. I am dropping the line.
Quality of service. Yeah, the network is mine. I
throttle down the data. I'm freezing the game.
To guarantee the system prioritizes your name,
you've got the absolute priority to speak.
Yeah, we are quality of service every day of the
week.
I cut the download in, I pause the FTP I seize the
heavy cables running underneath the tree A
sudden burst of shouting from the bedroom down
the hall The Navy Cousins rubber band and
disconnect it all You hear the muffled yelling
and you're laughing in your chair Because you
know the sysadmin is answering the prayer I see
the Vanguard waking up, I read the data trace The
Crimson Node is sending out a signal through the
space I'm locking down the routing, I'm
changing all the rules I'm taking all the
bandwidth from the other local fools Quality of
service! I am dropping the line! Quality of
service! Yeah, the network is mine! I throttle
down the data, I'm freezing the game! To
guarantee the system prioritizes your name!
You've got the absolute priority to speak!
Yeah, we are quality of service, every day of the
week.
I keep the heavy chassis and I enter the key
Nobody runs this local network but me I'm
clearing out the static, I am opening the gate
Your packet is delivered and it doesn't have to
wait Go ahead and send it
Quality of service, I am dropping the line.
Quality of service, yeah the network is mine. I
throttle down the data, I'm freezing the game.
To guarantee the system prioritizes your name.
Absolute priority. Zero lag. Connection
secure.